<resources>
    <string name="app_name">TherapEase</string>
    <string name="breath_count">Breath Count</string>
    <string name="todo">TODO</string>
    <string name="_5_november_2015">5 November 2015</string>
    <string name="choosedate">Choose Date</string>
    <string name="datechoosen">Date Chosen :</string>
    <!-- Setting dialog -->
    <string name="settings_title">Settings</string>
    <string name="settings_text_inhale">Inhale</string>
    <string name="settings_text_exhale">Exhale</string>
    <string name="settings_text_hold">Hold</string>
    <string name="settings_text_close">Close</string>
    <string name="zero">00:00</string>
    <string name="jan">January</string>
    <string name="jul">July</string>
    <string name="jun">June</string>
    <string name="mar">March</string>
    <string name="feb">February</string>
    <string name="aug">August</string>
    <string name="apr">April</string>
    <string name="may">May</string>
    <string name="dec">December</string>
    <string name="sep">September</string>
    <string name="oct">October</string>
    <string name="nov">November</string>
    <string name="_200">200</string>
    <string name="glasses">Glasses</string>
    <string name="valid_date">Please select valid date</string>
    <string name="no_of_breath">Number of breaths you have taken</string>
    <string name="breath_count_desc">Calculate the number of breaths you have taken so far (i.e.,since your birth).</string>


    <string name="quote1">“We cannot solve problems with the kind of thinking we employed when we came up with them.” \n\n— Albert Einstein.</string>
    <string name="quote2">“Learn as if you will live forever, live like you will die tomorrow.” \n\n— Mahatma Gandhi</string>
    <string name="quote3">“Stay away from those people who try to disparage your ambitions. Small minds will always do that, but great minds will give you a feeling that you can become great too.” \n\n— Mark Twain</string>
    <string name="quote4">“When you give joy to other people, you get more joy in return. You should give a good thought to happiness that you can give out.” \n\n— Eleanor Roosevelt</string>
    <string name="quote5">“When you change your thoughts, remember to also change your world.” \n\n—Norman Vincent Peale</string>
    <string name="quote6">“It is only when we take chances, when our lives improve. The initial and the most difficult risk that we need to take is to become honest.\n\n—Walter Anderson</string>
    <string name="quote7">“Nature has given us all the pieces required to achieve exceptional wellness and health, but has left it to us to put these pieces together.” \n\n—Diane McLaren</string>
    <string name="quote8">"Success is not final; failure is not fatal: It is the courage to continue that counts." \n\n— Winston S. Churchill</string>
    <string name="quote9">"It is better to fail in originality than to succeed in imitation." \n\n— Herman Melville</string>
    <string name="quote10">"The road to success and the road to failure are almost exactly the same." \n\n— Colin R. Davis</string>
    <string name="quote11">“Success usually comes to those who are too busy looking for it.” \n\n— Henry David Thoreau</string>
    <string name="quote12">“Develop success from failures. Discouragement and failure are two of the surest stepping stones to success.” \n\n— Dale Carnegie</string>
    <string name="quote13">“The pessimist sees difficulty in every opportunity. The optimist sees opportunity in every difficulty." \n\n— Winston Churchill</string>
    <string name="quote14">“Don’t let yesterday take up too much of today.” \n\n— Will Rogers</string>
    <string name="quote15">“If you are working on something that you really care about, you don’t have to be pushed. The vision pulls you.” \n\n— Steve Jobs</string>
    <string name="quote16">“Experience is a hard teacher because she gives the test first, the lesson afterwards.” \n\n— Vernon Sanders Law</string>
    <string name="quote17">“Experience is a hard teacher because she gives the test first, the lesson afterwards.” \n\n— Vernon Sanders Law</string>
    <string name="quote18">“To know how much there is to know is the beginning of learning to live.”\n\n — Dorothy West</string>
    <string name="quote19">“Goal setting is the secret to a compelling future.” \n\n— Tony Robbins</string>
    <string name="quote20">“Concentrate all your thoughts upon the work in hand. The sun rays do not burn until brought to a focus. “ \n\n— Alexander Graham Bell</string>


</resources>